https://www.123wigs.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At 123wigs.com, we know how important real privacy is to you. Therefore, we have written a very upfront privacy policy. We’ve even summed it all up in the first paragraph for you.
SummaryWe collect some personal information from you when you place an order or sign up for our newsletter. We do not rent, share or sell this information. We do not send out spam. We will not contact you without your permission. We will not change this privacy policy without notifying you first. For details on these policies, please read on.
Personal Information we collectWhen you place an order or sign up for membership, we collect personal information from you including your name, address, telephone number and email address. When you sign up for our newsletter, we collect your email address only.
What happens to the information?We use this information to send you our newsletter (if you request it), fulfill your order and notify you of the status of your orders. We will not rent, share or sell your data with any other parties. If, at some point our company is purchased by or merges with another company, we will ensure that whatever we become, your personal data will enjoy the same protections that is has in this document.
*NOTE information in our system may be released to authorities as part of any legal investigation or under court order should the situation arise.
IP AddressesWe collect IP Addresses whenever you browse our website. Our server uses this address to keep shopping carts for different customers. Separate and other store related functions. We also collect IP Addresses for all contact to our server to monitor any unauthorized access.
CookiesOur server uses cookies to keep individual shopping carts and internet users separate. We also use cookies to retain client information for convenience. We do not use any 3rd party advertisers with cookies.
PRODUCTS
Wigs
Hairpieces
Extensions
Costume
Accessories
Customer Service
About
receive 20% off your next purchase!
Sign Up
please wait...
close
Sign up & Save 20%
Sign up to receive the latest 123Wigs updates on new collections, exclusive promotions and news.
Subscribers will receive a coupon code for 20% off their first order.
close
